const mockData = {
  categories: [
    {
      id: 1,
      name: "일상 단어",
      flashcards: [
        { id: 901, question: "사전", answer: "Dictionary", hint: "D" },
        { id: 902, question: "이력서", answer: "Resume", hint: "R" },
        { id: 903, question: "연락처", answer: "Contact", hint: "C" },
        { id: 904, question: "편지", answer: "Letter", hint: "L" },
        { id: 905, question: "재료", answer: "Material", hint: "M" },
      ],
    },
    {
      id: 2,
      name: "교통 수단",
      flashcards: [
        { id: 1001, question: "자동차", answer: "Car", hint: "C" },
        { id: 1002, question: "비행기", answer: "Airplane", hint: "A" },
        { id: 1003, question: "기차", answer: "Train", hint: "T" },
        { id: 1004, question: "배", answer: "Ship", hint: "S" },
        { id: 1005, question: "자전거", answer: "Bicycle", hint: "B" },
      ],
    },
    {
      id: 3,
      name: "음식",
      flashcards: [
        { id: 1101, question: "밥", answer: "Rice", hint: "R" },
        { id: 1102, question: "김치", answer: "Kimchi", hint: "K" },
        { id: 1103, question: "커피", answer: "Coffee", hint: "C" },
        { id: 1104, question: "빵", answer: "Bread", hint: "B" },
        { id: 1105, question: "물", answer: "Water", hint: "W" },
      ],
    },
  ],
};

export default mockData;
